Destroy enemy troops near the southern village. Use caution when moving through ravines - enemy troops may stage ambushes on their heights. Use the swarm control (<CTRL> + <tap the ground> or M button on the left) while moving troops.

Don't try hitting them right up the middle, it would be best to attack from different directions.  Don't forget to support your attacks with aviation and long-range artillery.