The Red Army has started an offensive to dislodge our troops from their position near the bridge.  We must hold our position and eliminate the attackers.

Anti-tank mines (marked with red flags) can damage Soviet tank tracks, cutting off their infantry from tank support. Your best tactic would be to use your entrenched positions to cut down the assaulting infantry instead of going into the field to eliminate them.  

Basic Shortcuts: <F5> - Quicksave, <F8> - Quickload,  - Menu,  - Help, <Space> - Pause