Select armor units and use aggressive movement (the M button on the left) at the designated point (the purple arrow on the minimap.) You can also press the M button on the left and then tap the destination to move ready to fight.

Remember that you can open the help window anytime from the menu and the objectives window with the Show Last Objective button. Also, you can press the <SPACE> bar to pause the game.