Air reconnaissance shows that the enemy is well prepared and has superior forces. He has also called out his fighter planes to patrol over the town, making it even more dangerous for our forces. Now that our interceptors are available, you need to call them in to take out the enemy fighters.  To call your fighters, click on the plane button to the right of the minimap, then click the "Fighter" button (blinking).  tap the ground over their destination point (the purple arrow on the minimap).