The enemy has deployed their heavy anti-aircraft guns. Since these guns can shoot at high-altitude targets, we can't risk using our heavy bombers.  You need to use your sniper to eliminate their crews.  Use the transport plane to paradrop a scout at the designated area. To call a paratrooper plane click the plane button to the right of the minimap, then click the "Paratrooper plane" button (blinking) and tap the ground at the destination point.  Eliminating those gun crews will be the toughest part of your mission, once thats done, we'll send in our fly-boys to finish the job.