Create a frame by moving the cursor over multiple units that you want to select while holding the left mouse button down. When the frame covers ALL the units you wish to select release the mouse button. 
To reset the selection, tap on unoccupied terrain. You can select multiple units of the same type by double taping on any unit of this type.  Use the Q button on the left to include or exclude selected units.
Select ALL units to complete objective.